# **Ayush Dutta**

+91 8100608233 | <u>dutta\_ayush@srmap.edu.in</u> | <u>github/spirizeon</u> | <u>linkedin/ayushduttasrmap</u> | <u>Blog\_page</u>

### about

Ayush Dutta is a passionate cybersecurity specialist and a dedicated technologist, currently pursuing a Bachelor of Technology in Cybersecurity. With a strong foundation in programming languages and web security tools, Ayush has demonstrated leadership and innovation in his roles. A continuous learner, Ayush is actively enhancing his skills through various resources and TryHackMe rooms: focusing on web security and Linux exploitation. His commitment to technology, cybersecurity, and continuous learning makes him a valuable asset in the tech community.

### education.

## **SRM University Andhra Pradesh**

7/2023 - Present

Bachelor of Technology (CyberSecurity specialisation)

## Delhi Public School Ruby Park, Kolkata

2021 - 2023

Intermediate, Pure Sciences

### Delhi Public School STS, Dhaka

2019-2021

Matriculation

## work experience.

## Google Developer Students Club - Indian Institute of Technology, Madras

07/2023 - Present

Mentor, Linux & system commands

Tamil Nadu, India

- Became one of the founding volunteers for GDSC IITM's Linux division
- Hosted tech talk: Switching to Linux
- Leading a community of 100+ in system commands, troubleshooting and OS related problems

### Centre for Drone Techonology - SRM University, Andhra Pradesh

08/2023 - Present

Member, Drone Vision Developer

Amravati, India

- Building fine-tuned models for object and person detection and recognition
- · Working on edge-based tracking applications for unmanned aerial vehicles

## skills.

### programming languages

• Python, Bash, Rust, C, Lua

## web security tools

• Gobuster, GNU-utils, Burp-suite, Nmap, Debian Linux, Arch Linux

### data science & machine learning

• NumPy, Pandas, scikit-learn, Pytorch, HuggingFace

### databases

· MySQL, SQLite

#### other tools

• Git, GitHub, VS Code, Linux (Arch btw), NeoVim, Docker